{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Jīnnián",
      "answer": "今年"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nián",
      "answer": "年"
    },
    {
      "question": "Suì",
      "answer": "岁"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zěnme yàng",
      "answer": "怎么样"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jīntiān",
      "answer": "今天"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kè",
      "answer": "课"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xīngqí",
      "answer": "星期"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shàngwǔ",
      "answer": "上午"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shàng",
      "answer": "上"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiàwǔ",
      "answer": "下午"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xià",
      "answer": "下"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xīngqírì",
      "answer": "星期日"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shēngrì",
      "answer": "生日"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shēng",
      "answer": "生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duōdà",
      "answer": "多大"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duō",
      "answer": "多"
    },
    {
      "question": "dà",
      "answer": "大"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chūshēng",
      "answer": "出生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chū",
      "answer": "出"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shǔ",
      "answer": "属"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jùhuì",
      "answer": "聚会"
    },
    {
      "question": "huì",
      "answer": "会"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhùhè",
      "answer": "祝贺"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhù",
      "answer": "祝"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cānjiā",
      "answer": "参加"
    },
    {
      "question": "Le",
      "answer": "了"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chī",
      "answer": "吃"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dàngāo",
      "answer": "蛋糕"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dàn",
      "answer": "蛋"
    },
    {
      "question": "gāo",
      "answer": "糕"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mǎi",
      "answer": "买"
    },
    {
      "question": "Píng",
      "answer": "瓶"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hóng pútáojiǔ",
      "answer": "红葡萄酒"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hóng",
      "answer": "红"
    },
    {
      "question": "pútáo",
      "answer": "葡萄"
    },
    {
      "question": "jiǔ",
      "answer": "酒"
    },
    {
      "question": "Běijīng",
      "answer": "北京"
    }
  ]
}
